zenoviaexchange.com 2014-09-22

# Zenovia Digital Exchange – Website Privacy Policy

This information and the privacy statement below apply to our corporate website, ZenoviaExchange.com. If you have any questions about this policy, email privacy@zenoviaexchange.com. This policy does not apply to use of the Zenovia platform for delivering online advertising, including the use of the Zenovia Platform on ZenoviaExchange.com. For information about privacy on the Zenovia Platform click here. Zenoviaexchange.com may contain content or links to content or services provided by third parties. This policy does not apply to the practices of those third parties.

#### Collection, Use, and Retention of Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

We collect PII via this website when it is provided to us. The PII we collect may include name, address, phone number, email address, or any other information provided to us. We use the PII collected via this website for business purposes, such as marketing, recruiting and hiring, responding to general inquiries or customer support requests, and in the course of providing services to customers. We retain the PII collected via the website indefinitely, unless otherwise specified, or until we delete the PII pursuant to a request from the subject of the PII.

#### Collection, Use, and Retention of Non-PII

We collect non-PII on our website using cookies, web beacons, and tags for the operation of the site (e.g. managing user sessions), including analyzing site usage, detecting and preventing malicious behavior on the site, and improving the content and organization of the site. We also engage other companies that will use similar methods to collect non-PII on our website for analyzing site usage. We use the Zenovia Platform on ZenoviaExchange.com to collect non-PII to be used for advertising our business on other websites. The Zenovia Platform Privacy Statement applies to this collection and use of information.

#### Information Sharing

We will not rent, share, or sell to third parties the PII we collect via ZenoviaExchange.com, except for the reasons stated in this Privacy Statement. We may share non-PII or PII with affiliates, subsidiaries, vendors, or other third parties to perform services on our behalf that are related to marketing and operating Zenovia’s business.

We may disclose your information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. We may transfer information, including any PII, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change.

#### Information about children

This site is not intended for, or designed to attract, children. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is an individual under the age of 13.

#### Your Choices

We will provide reasonable opportunity for individuals to access, update, or delete PII about them that we have in our possession. We will not use PII provided to us for purposes incompatible with the purpose for which it was provided without obtaining authorization from the subject of the information. For sensitive information, as required by the Safe Harbor Principles, we will obtain authorization prior to sharing the information or using it for a purpose other than that for which it was collected. For choices relating to interest-based advertising on the Zenovia Platform, see the Zenovia Platform Privacy Statement [link].

#### Changes to this Policy

We may from time to time change our practices with regard to information collected and used on Zenoviaexchange.com. Changes will be reflected in this Privacy Statement. However, if we were to make material changes, those changes would not, without authorization, be applied to information collected prior to the changes.

#### Questions?

If you have questions or requests regarding our collection and use of information, please email us at privacy@zenoviaexchange.com.

…Last Updated: 29 March 2012
